[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What US President was a peanut farmer from the south?", "correct_answer": "Jimmy Carter", "incorrect_answers": ["John Quincy Adams", "Abe Lincoln", "George W Bush"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The capital city of this US state is Trenton, and its largest city is Newark.", "correct_answer": "New Jersey", "incorrect_answers": ["Montana", "New Hampshire", "New Mexico"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the planet Uranus named after?", "correct_answer": "The Greek god of the sky", "incorrect_answers": ["The Egyptian god of the sky", "The Roman god of the sky", "The Babylonian god of the sky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The mudpuppy can produce noise.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The skin has its own ecosystems of microorganisms, including yeasts and bacteria, which cannot be removed by washing.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What song from the Another Cinderella Story is performed by Drew Seeley and Selena Gomez?", "correct_answer": "New Classic", "incorrect_answers": ["No Average Angel", "Valentine\u2019s Dance Tango", "Tell Me Something I Don\u2019t Know"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The tallest mountain peak in the US is Mount McKinley. This is the second tallest.", "correct_answer": "Mount Saint Elias", "incorrect_answers": ["Glacier Peak", "Mount Washington", "Gannett Peak"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This agent was patented by LOreal.  It is stated to be the only sure UVA sun filter as its molecule remains unaffected by solar energy. Thus, it provides effective and long-lasting sun protection.", "correct_answer": "Mexoryl SX", "incorrect_answers": ["Aminexil", "Adenosinetriphosphate", "Ceramides"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the 80s movie 48 Hrs. set?", "correct_answer": "San Francisco", "incorrect_answers": ["Chicago", "San Diego", "Florida"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This American professional basketball player, nicknamed The Pearl, was known for his flamboyant dribbling and play-making.", "correct_answer": "Earl Monroe", "incorrect_answers": ["Tiny Archibald", "Sam Jones", "Paul Silas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Pretty Woman how much money does Edward Lewis pay Julia Roberts character to be his escort?", "correct_answer": "$3,000", "incorrect_answers": ["$1,000", "$8,000", "$5,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actress played young soprano Christine in the movie The Phantom of the Opera?", "correct_answer": "Emmy Rossum", "incorrect_answers": ["Sarah Brightman", "Judy Garland", "Lindsay Lohan"]}]